<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guidelines on Class Homepage</title>
    <link>/docs/guidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guidelines on Class Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/docs/guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>/docs/guidelines/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/guidelines/general/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;general&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  General&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#general&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;attendance&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Attendance&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#attendance&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our class will be offered on campus for both Undergrad (4641) and Grad (7641). Lectures might be recorded IF class has the recording system. Any class that I am able to record [which sometimes does not work even if we have the recording system in place], I will make it available to all students (both undergrad and grad) by the end of the day. The attendance is required for both undergrad and grad. Having students in the class helps me and my students A LOT work with each other for a better environment to facilitate learning. Trust me it will be fun and you will give me a lot of energy to teach better. The fact that you need to listen to the lectures without fast-forwarding me can help you learn the materials much better and you will have the chance to ask questions if you are confused anywhere in the lectures. Also, &lt;strong&gt;the class attendance will be counted toward your class participation at the end of semester.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>/docs/guidelines/office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/guidelines/office-hours/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;office-hours&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Office Hours&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#office-hours&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Overview&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#overview&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Office hours will be in a hybrid mode for both online and in-person. We will send an announcement on Ed regarding office hours and when it will start. Please follow the instruction on the Excel Sheet provided on Canvas under &lt;strong&gt;Announcements/Office Hours Link&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;a href=&#34;https://gatech.instructure.com/courses/467214/discussion_topics/2147177&#34;&gt;Undergrad&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://gatech.instructure.com/courses/467206/discussion_topics/2147225&#34;&gt;Grad&lt;/a&gt;] to signup for a 15-minutes slot with one of the TAs. You need to add your name and question of interest. If you require more than 15 minutes, please advise the TAs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
